John A. Lomax and Alan Lomax papers
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Correspondence, 1925-1952 and undated
  - Subseries I: John A. Lomax, 1933-1952 and undated
    - September-October 1935 (Box-folder 1/32)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1935-09-07
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1935-09-23
      - T.J Guinan to John A. Lomax, 1935-09-25
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1935-09-30
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1935-10-02
      - Library of Congress M and Delivery Division to Railway Express Agency, 1935-10-02
    - November 1935 (Box-folder 1/34)
      - Lincoln Thompson to John A. Lomax, 1935-11-08
        Includes note from Lomax to Strunk, 1935-11-16
      - Library of Congress Music Division to John A. Lomax, 1935-11-14
      - Oliver Strunk, Jr. to John A. Lomax, 1935-11-18
      - John A. Lomax to Robert M. Lester, 1935-11-26
      - Herbert Putnam to Oliver Strunk, Jr., 1935-11-29
    - December 1935-June 1936 (Box-folder 1/35)
      - John A. Lomax to Lincoln Thompson, 1935-12-12
      - Allen R. Boyd to John A. Lomax, 1936-01-14
        Library of Congress Executive Assistant
      - John A. Lomax to Allen R. Boyd, 1936-01-30
      - John A. Lomax to Oliver Strunk, Jr., 1936-03-27
      - Ruby Pickens Tartt to Miss Miles, 1936
        "Reminiscences"
      - Paul G. Brewster to John A. Lomax, 1936-06-01
    - May-June 1936 (Box-folder 1/37)
      - John A. Lomax to Oliver Strunk, Jr., 1936-05-02
      - John A. Lomax to Oliver Strunk, Jr., 1936-05-06
      - Oliver Strunk, Jr. to Waldo G. Leland, 1936-05-07
        ACLS
      - Oliver Strunk, Jr. to Library of Congress Music Division, 1936-05-09
      - Richard H. Kimball to John A. Lomax, 1936-05-18
        Allen Prothero
      - John A. Lomax to Oliver Strunk, Jr., 1936-06-01
      - Oliver Strunk, Jr. to Library of Congress Music Division, 1936-06-06
      - Oliver Strunk, Jr. to Library of Congress Music Division, 1936-06-09
      - David Rubic to Library of Congress Music Division, 1936-06-09
        Library of Congress Hispanic Division
    - July-August 1936 (Box-folder 1/38)
      - Edward N. Waters to Lincoln Thompson, 1936-07-09
      - Library of Congress Music Division to John A. Lomax, 1936-08-29
        Voucher
      - John A. Lomax to Oliver Strunk, Jr., 1936-08-11
      - John A. Lomax to Oliver Strunk, Jr., 1936-08-14
      - James Putnam to John A. Lomax, 1936-08-18
        Macmillan Company; Cowboy Songs revision
      - Oliver Strunk, Jr. to John A. Lomax, 1936-08-25
    - September-December 1936 (Box-folder 1/39)
      - Herbert Putnam to H.T. Parlin, 1936-09-26
      - Herbert Putnam to John A. Lomax, 1936-09-26
      - John A. Lomax to Oliver Strunk, Jr., 1936-10-20
      - Library of Congress Music Division to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1936-11-23
      - Library of Congress Music Division to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1936-12-05
      - Lincoln Thompson to John A. Lomax, 1936-12-14
      - John A. Lomax to Herbert Putnam, 1936-12-16
      - Oliver Strunk, Jr. to Library of Congress Music Division, 1936-12-18
      - John A. Lomax to Herbert Putnam, 1936-12-17
      - L.L. Dantzler to John A. Lomax, 1936-12-18
        University of Kentucky
      - U.R. Bell to Henry G. Alsberg, 1936-12-19
      - John A. Lomax to L.L. Dantzler, 1936-12-23
    - February 1937 (Box-folder 1/41)
      - Henry Alsberg to John A. Lomax, 1937-02-02
      - Jackson Davis to John A. Lomax, 1937-02-20
        General Education Board
    - March 1937 (Box-folder 1/42)
      - Railway Express Agency to Oliver Strunk, Jr., 1937-03-15
      - John A. Lomax to Oliver Strunk, Jr., 1937-03-17
      - Oliver Strunk, Jr. to John A. Lomax, 1937-03-20
    - April 1937 (Box-folder 1/43)
      - Chandler family to John A. Lomax, 1937-04-16
      - John A. Lomax to Oliver Strunk, Jr., 1937-04-19
      - Clifford P. Lyons to John A. Lomax, 1937-04-27
        University of Florida
    - May 1937 (Box-folder 1/44)
      - John A. Lomax to Herbert Putnam, 1937-05-07
      - Paul S. Taylor to John A. Lomax, 1937-05-10
        University of California
      - John A. Lomax to Irvin F. Farr, 1937-05-24
      - Myrtle Miles to John A. Lomax, 1937-05-24
        Federal Writers' Project
      - John A. Lomax to Library of Congress Music Division, 1937-05-27
    - June 1937 (Box-folder 1/45)
      - John A. Lomax to George F. McKay, 1937-06-10
        University of Washington
      - John A. Lomax to Helen Waterhouse, 1937-06-11
      - A.W. Payne to John A. Lomax, 1937-06-20
      - Lucille Wilkin to John A. Lomax, 1937-06-21
      - Jean Thomas to John A. Lomax, 1937-06-26
      - Pearl R. Nye to John A. Lomax, 1937-06-29
        Receipt for services
      - Jean Thomas to John A. Lomax, 1937-06-29
    - July 1937 (Box-folder 1/46)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-07-03
      - A.P. Hudson to John A. Lomax, 1937-07-03
        University of North Carolina
      - John A. Lomax to A.P. Hudson, 1937-07-06
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Music Division, 1937-07-06
      - John A. Lomax to A.W. Payne, 1937-07-06
      - John A. Lomax to George F. McKay, 1937-07-06
      - John A. Lomax to Myrtle Miles, 1937-07-06
      - John A. Lomax to Genevieve Chandler, 1937-07-06
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-07-13
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-07-13
        Note to Alan
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1937-07-15
        Includes bill of landing
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1937-07-15
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-07-25
      - Library of Congress Mail and Delivery Division to Railway Express Agency, 1937-07-26
        Railway Express Agency; bill of lading
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1937-07-26
    - August 1937 (Box-folder 1/47)
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1937-08-04
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-08-07
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1937-08-12
      - John A. Lomax to Miss Whitfield, 1937-08-08
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-08-16
      - Harold Spivacke to Ruby Pickens Tartt, 1937-08-17
      - Harold Spivacke to Leo J. Palmer, 1937-08-17
        Wallkill Prison
      - Harold Spivacke to Minta Morgan, 1937-08-17
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-08-19
      - Kay Dealy to John A. Lomax, 1937-08-21
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1937-08-24
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-08-28
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-08-30
    - September 1937 (Box-folder 1/48)
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1937-09-01
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-09-09
      - Olive W. Dennis to John A. Lomax, 1937-09-14
        Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company
      - Federico de Onis to John A. Lomax, 1937-09-17
        Instituto de las Espanas
      - Library of Congress Music Division to Olive W. Dennis, 1937-09-30
    - October 1937 (Box-folder 1/49)
      - Sheila Marryat to John A. Lomax, 1937-10-01
        University of Alberta
      - W.P. Davis to John A. Lomax, 1937-10-01
        Old Fiddlers Convention, Galax, Virginia
      - Ernestine Taggard to John A. Lomax, 1937-10-01
        Scholastic; "Home on the Range"
      - H.M. Belden to John A. Lomax, 1937-10-02
      - Harold Spivacke to Joseph F. Smith, 1937-10-04
        University of Wisconsin
      - John A. Lomax to Sheila Marryat, 1937-10-06
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-10-06
      - John A. Lomax to Joseph F. Smith, 1937-10-04
      - John A. Lomax to Rosa Warren Wilson, 1937-10-12
      - John A. Lomax to Rosa Warren Wilson, 1937-10-12
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Music Division, 1937-10-19
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-10-14
      - Harold Spivacke to Herbert Putnam, 1937-10-18
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-10-29
    - November 1937 (Box-folder 1/50)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-11-01
      - J.L. Brown to John A. Lomax, 1937-11-01
      - Harold Spivacke to Thomas Rutherford, 1937-11-05
      - John A. Lomax to J.L. Brown, 1937-11-05
      - John A. Lomax to Olive W. Dennis, 1937-11-06
      - Charles Anthony to John A. Lomax, 1937-11-17
        Southern Methodist University
      - John A. Lomax to John A. Leslie, 1937-11-30
      - John A. Lomax to Charles Anthony, 1937-11-30
      - John A. Lomax to T.A. Hight, 1937-11-30
      - John A. Lomax to Minta Morgan, 1937-11-30
      - John A. Lomax to Nell Farrar, 1937-11-30
        Vocational School for Girls
      - John A. Lomax to unidentified, 1937
    - December 1937 (Box-folder 1/51)
      - Martha Beckwith to John A. Lomax, 1937-12-06
        Vassar College
      - Mitchell, John to John A. Lomax, 1937-12-28
    - January-June 1938 (Box-folder 2/52)
      - Susan S. Prink to John A. Lomax, 1938-01-11
      - John A. Lomax to Paul G. Brewster, 1938-02-01
      - Paul G. Brewster to John A. Lomax, 1938-02-08
      - Susan S. Prink to Edward N. Waters, 1938-03-07
      - Edward N. Waters to Susan S. Prink, 1938-03-08
      - John A. Lomax to Edward N. Waters, 1938-03-11
      - Edward N. Waters to Susan S. Prink, 1938-03-12
      - Edward N. Waters to Susan S. Prink, 1938-05-23
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-04-11
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1938-04-22
      - Edward N. Waters to John A. Lomax, 1938-06-24
    - July-December 1938 (Box-folder 2/53)
      - John A. Lomax to Edward N. Waters, 1938-07-10
      - John A. Lomax to J.L. Morrill, 1938-09-19
        Ohio State University
      - John A. Lomax, Sr. to Martina McDonald, 1938-09-21
      - Felix Greene to John A. Lomax, 1938-10-03
        British Broadcasting Company
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-09
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-10
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1938-10-12
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-15
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1938-10-17
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1938-10-21
      - Glen Perrins to John A. Lomax, 1938-10-28
        Ogden Standard Examiner
      - William H. Vann to John A. Lomax, 1938-11-01
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-12-13
      - Macmillan Company to John A. Lomax, 1938-12-19
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1938-12-19
      - John A. Lomax to unidentified, 1938-12
        Lomax family holiday card
      - Edward Crane to John A. Lomax, 1938
      - Ben Robertson to John A. Lomax, 1938-12-28
    - January 1939 (Box-folder 2/54)
      - James Putnam to John A. Lomax, 1939-01-12
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-01-15
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-01-15
      - D. Walfert to John A. Lomax, 1939-01-18
        Brooklyn College
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-01-20
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-01-24
      - John A. Lomax to Edward N. Waters, 1939-01-24
      - John A. Lomax to Frank Megill, 1939-01-25
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-01-30
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-01-30
      - Felix Greene to John A. Lomax, 1939-01-31
    - February 1939 (Box-folder 2/55)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-02-04
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-02-07
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-02-07
      - Felix Greene to Harold Spivacke, 1939-02-07
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-02-10
      - Edward N. Waters to John A. Lomax, 1939-02-10
      - Edward N. Waters to Felix Greene, 1939-02-10
      - Felix Greene to Edward N. Waters, 1939-02-11
      - Annette Ebsen to John A. Lomax, 1939-02-20
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-02-23
      - P. Ashbey to John A. Lomax, 1939-02-27
        Wier Long Leaf Lumber Company; Henry Truvillion
    - March 1939 (Box-folder 2/56)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-03-04
      - John A. Lomax to unidentified, 1939-03-06
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-03-06
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-03-08
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-03-11
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-03-12
      - Oscar Fox to John A. Lomax, 1939-03-14
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-03-15
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-03-16
      - Harold Spivacke to Librarian of Congress, 1939-03-17
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-03-20
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1939-03-24
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-03-26
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-03-26
      - John A. Lomax to H.W. Broome, 1939-03-26
      - John A. Lomax to A.J. Dornbrush, 1939-03-27
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-03-28
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-03-29
    - April 1939 (Box-folder 2/57)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-04-08
      - Ruby Terrill Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-04-10
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-04-13
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-04-14
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-04-15
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-04-25
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-04-26
      - H.W. Broome to John A. Lomax, 1939-04
        Encl. H.W. Broome to A.J. Dornbush
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-04-28
    - May 1939 (Box-folder 2/58)
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-05-03
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-09
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-09
      - Jess Morris to John A. Lomax, 1939-05-10
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-12
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-13
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-05-15
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-16
        Café Texan
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-05-17
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-18
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-05-19
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1939-05-22
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-22
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-24
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-05-24
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-24
      - Benjamin A. Botkin to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-25
        Works Progress Administration
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-26
      - Southeastern Express Company to John A. Lomax, 1939-05-26
        Southeastern Express Company
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1939-05-29
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-29
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-05-30
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-05-31
    - June 1939 (Box-folder 2/59)
      - Harold Spivacke to Jacob Evanson, 1939-06-05
      - Jacob Evanson to John A. Lomax, 1939-06-05
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1939-06-08
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-06-08
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-06-08
      - Harold Spivacke to Librarian of Congress, 1939-06-27
    - July 1939 (Box-folder 2/60)
      - Alton C. Morris to John A. Lomax, 1939-07-06
        Southern Folkore Quarterly
      - H.R. Weaver to John A. Lomax, 1939-07-06
        Southwestern Improvement Company
      - Hon. George H. Mahon to John A. Lomax, 1939-07-07
      - Paul G. Brewster to John A. Lomax, 1939-07-12
        University of Missouri
      - H.R. Weaver to John A. Lomax, 1939-07-20
        Southwestern Lumber Company of New Jersey
      - John A. Lomax to John Harrington Cox, 1939-07-25
        University of West Virginia
    - August 1939 (Box-folder 2/61)
      - Burk, Genevieve S. to John A. Lomax, 1939-08-21
      - Edward N. Waters to Library of Congress Disbursing Office, 1939-08-21
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-08-28
    - September-November 1939 (Box-folder 2/62)
      - C.E. Tucker to John A. Lomax, 1939-09-01
        Oliver Ditson Company
      - Edith Cook Smith to John A. Lomax, 1939-10-05
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-10-10
      - Harold Spivacke to J.A. Rickard, 1939-10-23
        Texas College of Arts and Industries
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-11-01
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-11-15
      - E.C. Ball to John A. Lomax, 1939-11-20
      - Dyke, Burt to John A. Lomax, 1939-11-23
    - December 1939 (Box-folder 2/65)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-12-05
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1939-12-07
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1939-12-20
      - Richard Donovan to John A. Lomax, 1939-12-22
      - M.M. Gouger to John A. Lomax, 1939-12-26
      - Clara MacGowan to John A. Lomax, 1939-12-26
        National Education Association
    - January 1940 (Box-folder 2/66)
      - John A. Lomax to M.M. Gouger, 1940-01-03
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-01-03
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1940-01-04
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-01-04
      - Roy Harris to John A. Lomax, 1940-01-04
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-01-06
      - Clara MacGowan to John A. Lomax, 1940-01-07
      - Jess Morris to John A. Lomax, 1940-01-13
      - Harold Spivacke to Librarian of Congress, 1940-01-15
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1940-01-16
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-01-17
      - John A. Lomax to E.H. Latham, 1940-01-17
      - Roy [Bedi?] Bedichek to John A. Lomax, 1940-01-24
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1940-01-24
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1940-01-24
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-01-28
    - February 1940 (Box-folder 2/67)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-02-13
    - March-April 1940 (Box-folder 2/68)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-03-12
      - George Storer Hoke to John A. Lomax, 1940-03-15
      - John A. Lomax to unidentified, 1940-03-28
      - Ada S. Benedict to John A. Lomax, 1940-04-07
      - Mary Flescher to Harold Spivacke, 1940-04-18
      - Ada S. Benedict to John A. Lomax, 1940-04-29
        Encl. Edward Crane and Mabel Major
      - Chandler family to Ruby Terrill Lomax, 1940-04-30
    - May 1940 (Box-folder 2/70)
      - Edward N. Waters to Mary Flescher, 1940-05-01
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1940-05-07
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-05-10
      - John A. Lomax to Jess Morris, 1940-05-10
      - Jess Morris to John A. Lomax, 1940-05-12
      - Earl Robinson to John A. Lomax, 1940-05-11
      - Unidentified to John A. Lomax, 1940
        "Rosalie, the Prairie Flower"
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-05-13
      - Carl Sandburg to John A. Lomax, 1940-05-28
    - June 1940 (Box-folder 2/71)
      - J.A. Rickard to Harold Spivacke, 1940-06-05
      - Harold Spivacke to J.A. Rickard, 1940-06-10 (Box-folder 2/72)
    - July 1940
      - H.C. Darnell to John A. Lomax, 1940-07-09 (Box-folder 2/72)
        RCA Manufacturing Co., Inc.
      - Jess Morris to John A. Lomax, 1940-07-10
      - J.A. Rickard to Harold Spivacke, 1940-07-17
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1940-07-29
    - August 1940 (Box-folder 2/73)
      - Ruth Burchenal to John A. Lomax, 1940-08-01
        Folk Arts Center
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-08-01
      - Marquis E. Shattuck to John A. Lomax, 1940-08-07
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1940-08-08
        Includes note to Alan
      - James Putnam to John A. Lomax, 1940-08-08
      - William F. Krahl to John A. Lomax, 1940-08-16
        Krahl Construction Co.
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-08-22
    - September 1940 (Box-folder 2/74)
      - John A. Lomax to Edward N. Waters, 1940-09-06
      - Mr. Hill to John A. Lomax, 1940-09-10
      - Library of Congress Disbursing Office to John A. Lomax, 1940-09-14
        Travel voucher
      - W.H. Hardman to John A. Lomax, 1940-09-20
      - T.A. Hight to John A. Lomax, 1940-09-22
      - James Putnam to John A. Lomax, 1940-09-30
      - Henry Nash Smith to John A. Lomax, 1940-09-30
    - October 1940 (Box-folder 2/75)
      - Jerome B. Wiesner to John A. Lomax, 1940-10-03
        Annotated by John A. Lomax
    - November 1940 (Box-folder 2/76)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-11-22
        Preparations for cataloging AFS discs
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-11-29
    - December 1940 (Box-folder 2/77)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-12-17
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1940-12
    - January 1941 (Box-folder 2/78)
      - Luna Sinclair to John A. Lomax, 1941-01-02
      - John A. Lomax to Luna Sinclair, 1941-01-14
      - Howell, Sostkin and Co. to John A. Lomax, 1941-01-08
      - John A. Lomax to Howell, Sostkin and Co., 1941-01-11
      - J.A. Rickard to John A. Lomax, 1941-01-08
      - L.J. Davidson to John A. Lomax, 1941-01-10
        University of Denver
      - John A. Lomax to E.C. Beck, 1941-01-11
        Central State Teachers College (Michigan)
      - John A. Lomax to Rev. B.D. Hall, 1941-01-14
      - John A. Lomax to J.W. Calhoun, 1941-01-14
      - John A. Lomax to L.J. Davidson, 1941-01-14
      - John A. Lomax to J.A. Rickard, 1941-01-17
      - John A. Lomax to George Lyman Kittredge, 1941-01-14
      - John A. Lomax to Edward Weeks, 1941-01-16
        Atlantic Monthly
      - John A. Lomax to Barrett Wendell, 1941-01-17
      - John A. Lomax to Gordon King, 1941-01-17
      - John A. Lomax to Ben Robinson, 1941-01-17
      - John A. Lomax to A.J. Putnam, 1941-01-17
      - John A. Lomax to Frances McLauskey, 1941-01-22
      - John A. Lomax to Frank Dobie, 1941-01-22
      - John A. Lomax to Dorothy Gebeaur, 1941-01-22
      - John A. Lomax to Edgar E. Witt, 1941-01-22
      - John A. Lomax to Josiah Combs, 1941-01-22
        Texas Christian University
      - Henry Nash Smith to John A. Lomax, 1941-01-28
      - John A. Lomax to Henry Nash Smith, 1941-01-29
      - Florrie Wade to John A. Lomax, 1941-01-31
    - February 1941 (Box-folder 2/79)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-02-08
      - Alfred C. Nelson to John A. Lomax, 1941-02-10
      - Raymond Weeks to John A. Lomax, 1941-02-10
    - March 1941 (Box-folder 2/80)
      - Col. I. Spalding to John A. Lomax, 1941-03-19
        U.S. War Department
    - April 1941 (Box-folder 2/81)
      - George A. Hill to John A. Lomax, 1941-04-18
        Houston Oil Company of Texas
      - Edward N. Waters to John A. Lomax, 1941-04-29
    - May 1941 (Box-folder 2/82)
      - John A. Lomax to Edward N. Waters, 1941-05-14
      - Mary R. Rogers to John A. Lomax, 1941-05-26
      - Bob Ledbetter to John A. Lomax, 1941-05-31
    - June 1941 (Box-folder 2/83)
      - Mary R. Rogers to John A. Lomax, 1941-06-03
      - June E. Stone to John A. Lomax, 1941-06-19
    - July 1941 (Box-folder 2/84)
      - James Sykes to John A. Lomax, 1941-07-01
        Colorado College
      - Theo Little to John A. Lomax, 1941-07-08
      - Down Beat magazine to John A. Lomax, 1941-07-17
        Down Beat magazine; Bessie Smith
      - Paul B. Johnson to John A. Lomax, 1941-07-17
        Governor of Mississippi; Bessie Smith
    - August 1941 (Box-folder 2/85)
      - John A. Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1941-08-22
      - Down Beat magazine to John A. Lomax, 1941-08-05
      - Walter Chandler to John A. Lomax, 1941-08-08
        Mayor of Memphis; Bessie Smith; Bessie Smith death certificate information
      - John A. Lomax to Edward N. Waters, 1941-08-09
    - September 1941 (Box-folder 2/86)
      - Harold Spivacke to John A. Lomax, 1941-09-02
      - James "Iron Head" Baker to John A. Lomax, 1941-09-02
      - James "Iron Head" Baker to John A. Lomax, 1941-09-04
      - C. Wardell St. John to John A. Lomax, 1941-09-05
        Choate School